The Cause is Myself, I am Ki Yamatojin.
I am Kosaku Koizumi.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, what is it today?
No, no, no. What is it today?
I didn't say, "What's today?
No, I'm not hosting.
Well, yes, yes, yes, yes, but...
I just thought I'd ask these guys.
How's it going?
No, no, no. Paint, Mr. Kousaku.
Paint.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
Aren't there four of them today?
No, sir.
No? Oh, I see.
No white sunglasses.
Well, well, well, but today we are going to go indoors.
We've been talking a lot lately...
Yes, sir.
Aren't you tired?
Yes, but... yes...
No, but not too much.
Why are you so tired?
After the show.
Why are you tired only here after the show?
It's been quite a while since the show ended.
I'm not tired at all.
Tell me you're tired.
We haven't started yet.
I'm not tired. I'm not tired.
Hey, hey, seriously, you're not going to start.
But yes, my muscles are a little sore.
So, um...
Yes, sir.
Today, I'd like to... I don't mean to refresh you, but...
Refresh
From the bottom of my heart.
Are you sure?
Yes. Thank you for the food.
Not at all.
Oh, you don't mind?
You're not going anywhere.
We'd like to go somewhere where we can refresh ourselves.
Let's go somewhere refreshing together.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Great, great.
Okay, let's go. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay, I'm off!
Ending
Written, composed, and arranged by Miku Hatsune
Thank you for watching!
Here we go.
Where do you think they're headed?
Isn't that it? I think.
A place to refresh.
Speaking of refreshment...
And to be healed.
Like a hot spring?
You don't go to hot springs.
Hot springs are nice.
Hot springs... hot springs... how are you going to get that on camera?
No, just do your best to put everything here in mosaic.
Just show his face.
If it's a mosaic, then don't show it.
You don't think so?
No, I don't think so.
Of course not.
The cameras didn't work, of course.
It's a big city.
I see.
So you're a healer.
Healing.
I wonder what else...
The eyes.
Eye protection
Oh, oh, oh, oh
eye care type
eye protection system
for example for example
For example?
Uh-huh.
For example...
There's a lot of things, right? You know, eye candy.
Hey.
Hint, hint.
A hint.
Well...
It's more like eye candy.
Yes, sir.
Cute.
Yeah.
Cute tips
Cute.
Well, can I ask you the answer?
Hey, yes, I'll give you a hint.
Don't ask me the answer right after I give you a hint.
That's cute.
What kind of quiz is that?
Okay, bye.
Like at the zoo?
How about...
I think there's a zoo down the street.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Then you're giving me a huge hint.
Yes, sir.
Biggest hint.
Is he close to Takato Okura?
A poodle.
A toy poodle?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on.
Am I hitting it hard?
We're getting really close.
Let's make friends with a poodle?
Today.
We're going to a place called...
Yes, sir.
Let's see...
This way.
Dog spa salon.
Aqua Maria?
Yes.
Well, I'm sure you're a little tired and stuff, so...
I'd like to refresh myself with my little dogs today.
I'd like to interact with the little dogs to refresh myself.
Isn't it great?
It's great!
Thank you very much.
What the hell is that? Hey!
It's soothing. It's definitely soothing.
Well, let's get to it. Let's go inside.
Shall we?
Yes, sir.
Hello.
You're a dog person.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ehhhh?
Oh, Shelly.
Long time no see.
Oh, hey.
You're so cute.
Oh, my God, she's so cute.
There are so many, many different breeds here.
Hey, hey, come here.
Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh.
So cute!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
They're all so friendly.
So cute
Hey, oh, this one is cute
I wonder what this girl's name is.
Carrie.
Oh, he's interested in Mike.
Hey.
He's cute.
Cute.
They're so friendly.
Yeah, they're friendly.
Oh, he brought me a ball.
He's so cute.
My muscles are sore already.
Ahem.
It's gone.
You hurt your muscles so fast.
It's so cute.
Oh, this is really...
It's my first time at a dog café.
First time, me too.
Me, too.
Hey, hey.
Hey, come here.
I love dogs. I love dogs so much.
You love dogs.
I love dogs. I love cats.
I love all animals.
I love dogs.
Oh, yes.
Oh, here he comes.
Here we go.
I want to... I want to... I want to do that.
Oh, I want to do that.
Hey, hey, come here, come here.
That's great.
Good job.
Mai olan
That's great.
I want to find it.
Oh, here it is!
Oh, sit down or something...
Red, sit down.
Oh, my gosh!
That's my favorite.
Oh, wait.
Here it comes.
Oh, fate!
I'm really excited about this.
Really, though.
It's so peaceful.
It really is.
It's really... it's really...
It makes me feel calm.
Really.
Oh, it's so cute!
This meat is so cute!
They're getting along so well.
When he first came in, he was a little...
I was like, "Who's that?
Look at him.
Look at us.
It's like we're dogs.
What's that supposed to mean?
That's different.
That's a little different.
But I feel like we're really getting to know each other a little bit.
Hey.
I'm so relieved. I'm sleeping.
You're asleep.
Yeah, I am.
I feel safe.
He's so relieved, he's sleeping like a baby.
He's so cute.
He's got such a cute smile, too.
You make me feel like a grandma.
You know...
That's enough.
Yes, ma'am.
They're so cute.
I've heard that you have dogs.
Which one is it?
Yes, ma'am.
Bye.
Bye. - Bye.
Oh, he's talking now.
Which one is it?
Bye.
Which one of you
Let's see if we can get a bye shot.
Oh, hey.
You know, a selfie.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Which one?
Uh-huh.
The one that's really...
With the dog.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'd like to play a game.
Let's take a picture.
I'm so ugly!
This is a difficult miracle picture.
I have to take a picture with the same breath.
I have to be conscious of my face.
I have to be conscious of my face, too.
Let's take a picture together, okay?
Let's take a picture together.
I'm already on it. I've got a plan.
Wait for it.
It's a plan.
Wait for it. Wait for it.
Oh, wait.
Come again.
Sorry.
I don't know, maybe if you lie down, they'll come.
Oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
It's coming.
Oh, my God.
Cadone.
This is Cadone.
He's snoring.
He snores a lot.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
That's hard.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is getting super fun.
what's going on?
Violets... violets... violets... violets...
Violets violets violets violets violets violets violets violets violets violets
Violets violets violets violets violets violets violets
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I can't leak my own
Shocking Facts
Shocking fact
Um, I'm not good at this
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, my God.
Toys. You're into toys, aren't you, boy?
You're the one, right?
You're crazy about toys.
Right? I'm sure of it.
Toys.
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh.
Oh, no.
In my head.
Thank you for watching.
Who's there? Who's there?
No, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Who is it? Who is it?
No, this is it.
Hey, how about this? It's pretty close-up.
How about this?
Is it doctored? Yes, it's doctored.
Is it doctored? I used the original app.
It's a no-fix competition.
Not really. I don't know.
Oh, that's nice.
Well, it's hard to tell.
Click.
Totoro? Let's work together.
I don't know.
Come on, let's work together.
It looks good on my eyes, too.
It's so good.
This one goes here, this one goes here.
Yes.
How are you? I'm sleeping like a baby.
Yes, sure.
Should I go back to sleep now?
Tom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't get up, don't get up, don't get up.
Oh, yeah.
That's nice.
This is better.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Come on, Kousaku, get it for me.
Yes, I'll get it.
I'll get it.
Yes, yes...
Oh, no...
I'm here...
I'm tired of it.
Yes.
I want to get on it and get this.
OK
Boober dot
me
I'm in.
I'm in!
The angle from here is too cute!
Wait, that's a really good picture.
I think I got a really good shot.
Sumichan, get over there!
But I'm sure we got some great shots.
Sumi-chan!
Well, you know... now, when I take selfies...
Your eyes are a little half-lidded...
You know how she was looking away?
Yes, I did.
So, there are a lot of things that make me uneasy.
Yes, sir.
What a surprise!
I'm using a very good camera this time.
Yes.
We're going to get through this.
Oh, my.
Yes, sir.
So, I've already
The good pictures are actually taken.
Are you sure you're getting it over here?
I'm getting it over here.
Then we don't need to take any more pictures.
But the pictures we took...
Yes, we did.
Isn't it cute?
It'll be a memory.
Yes, it will.
Tracing the vague horizon that seems to disappear...
forever connected to each other
The distance that flows, dancing on the cobblestone pavement.
The morning sun rises from the toes of my shoes.
I can hear the bells ringing, my urge for you burns.
Pang, pang, pang
So...
Yes, sir.
I'm so healed.
I'm healed... really healed.
Let's come again!
We'll see you in private, right?
In private, too.
It's really nice to pretend to be with a dog.
And, you know, the members who couldn't make it today.
Members who couldn't make it today.
I'd like to invite some of the members who couldn't come today.
I hope the seven of us can have fun together again.
I love you all!
Thank you very much for this opportunity.
I guess.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you very much.
See you soon.
See you soon!
Look at the pictures.
Yes, ma'am.
Bye bye.
I'm going to roll it out.
I'm going to focus on the water fall, right?
I'm going to do it.
It was supposed to be a healing project.
But you know what?
What I want to do now is
I'm the cause of the problem.
a test of courage
Like going to a haunted place.
You mean that one? Eiji Kida, alone.
Did you hear that? I said I was the cause.
Kida, alone...
I went to a haunted place alone.
Why not?
Just tell me why.
You know, people...
The moment our emotions overflow...
The moment they overflow with emotion, their true nature comes out.
Like when you get a big surprise.
When you're surprised...
When you say, "Wow!
Is this person going to run away?
Will he run away?
Or will he show his true colors?
I'd like to see that.
Which type do you think you are?
You'd leave everyone behind.
I'm very protective.
Don't worry about it.
I can't protect you.
I'd never protect you.
That's why I wanted to see what you'd do.
Like a project like that.
I'm really... I'm really...
I don't know.
I'm sure you'll make it happen.
Camping.
Camping is great.
Campfires and stuff.
Camping is booming these days.
I know a lot of people who enjoy it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I might be planning something like that in the future.
Please look forward to it.
Please let me know in the comments what kind of project you want me to do.
Please write in the comments.
What kind of projects you would like to see?
We may not be able to figure it out on our own.
We'd like to hear your opinions and grow together.
I'd like to grow together with you.
Is this a growth plan?
I'm looking forward to it.